mau5trap.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - mau5trap

**mau5trap is working hard to make sure that we comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). We value your privacy and your rights to own and control your personal data. We will never sell your data to third parties.**

The data that we do collect is meant to improve your user experience.

Unless otherwise stated, mau5trap Venture Limited and Epicwin Ltd. (collectively, “mau5trap”) are data controllers for the personal data we collect through mau5trap’s website, emails, and third-party applications where applicable (herein collectively referred to as “Services”) subject to this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) and under applicable data protection laws. Our website URL’s (individually and collectively, the “Site”) are:

  * mau5trap.com
  * live.deadmau5.com
  * mau5trapmerch.com
  * deadmau5merch.com

Each of the mau5trap entities, now in existence or hereafter created, separately make the disclosures in this Policy. The data protection officer of mau5trap can be contacted at the following email address: privacy@mau5trap.com.

This Policy explains what personal information we collect from you, either directly or indirectly, and how we use it. Please read this Policy carefully to understand how mau5trap (also referred to herein as “we”, “us”, and “our”) may collect, use, and share your personal information.

INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT 

We automatically collect information about you, your use of our website, or information collected by using cookies and similar technologies when you use, access or interact with our website. We may, for example, collect information about the type of device you use to access our websites, the operating system and version, your IP address, your general geographic location as indicated by your IP address, your browser type, the webpages you view on our websites, and whether and how you interact with content available on our websites.

Information Obtained from Other Sources. We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, such as music service partners and partners with whom we offer co-branded services or engage in joint marketing activities. We may also receive information about you from social media platforms. We protect data obtained from third parties according to the practices described in this Policy and we also apply any additional restrictions imposed by the source of data.

**For Your Reference, We May Collect the Following Data:**

  * Forms filled out by you including site registrations (where applicable)
  * Subscriptions or orders placed on the Site;
  * Participation in discussion boards or other social media functions on the Site;
  * Entering competitions, promotions, or surveys;
  * Correspondence with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise;
  * Reporting a problem or requesting support for the Site

The customer interactions with mau5trap are broken down into the following segments:

Basic User Data. This includes name, email address, IP address, and information provided by cookies or similar technology to share news about events and products offered by mau5trap. The IP address helps us to understand geographic information about our websites’ visitors to better improve our website. It is our legitimate interest to process your personal data for these purposes.

Purchasing Data. Once you have decided to buy a mau5trap product including mau5trap or mau5trap’s artist branded merchandise (“Products”), we offer a way for customers to buy directly from us at our Site.

To effectuate such transactions, we collect: your name, phone number (optional), email address, delivery/shipping address, and payment information. This information is used solely to complete your transaction, follow up with you about your purchase, help with any delivery issues, handle returns, and other issues related to the purchase of your mau5trap Products. We do not store any payment or credit card information. We only use payment information in connection with the purchase of mau5trap Products.

We collect: your name, phone number, email address, location data, your password and IP address. Please note, your password is stored using one-way hash, which means that it cannot be recovered (or disclosed) by anyone, including mau5trap.

Why: We collect this information to help get your mau5trap services processing correctly. We also use your email to send you mau5trap-related notifications, such as promotional messages, information about mau5trap Products and/or Services, and to share exciting mau5trap news and Product offerings. It is our legitimate interest to process your personal data for these purposes.

Registration Data. This data includes your email address, location, language preference, Product serial number, IP address, and mau5trap account login information (as described above).

HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION 

mau5trap uses the data we collect to provide you with the mau5trap Products and Services we offer, which includes using data to improve and personalize your experiences. We also use the data to communicate with you, for example, informing you about your account, new mau5trap Products or Services available, security and other types of updates.

**mau5trap Uses the Data for The Following Purposes:**

  * We use data to respond to customer inquiries, diagnose Product problems, and provide other customer care and support services. This processing is necessary to serve our legitimate interest.
  * We continually use data for research purposes and to develop and improve our mau5trap Products and Services, including maintaining and improving the performance of our mau5trap Services, using search queries and clicks to improve the relevance of search results and using usage data to determine what new features to prioritize. This processing is necessary to serve our legitimate interest.
  * We use data to protect the security and safety of our mau5trap Products and our customers, to detect and prevent fraud, to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. This processing is necessary to serve our legitimate interest.
  * We use data to develop aggregate analysis and business intelligence that enable us to operate, protect, make informed decisions, and report on the performance of our business. This processing is necessary to serve our legitimate interest.
  * We use the data we collect to deliver and personalize our communications with you. For example, we may contact you by email or other means of electronic communication mau5trap to inform you about new mau5trap Products or Services, and security updates, to update you on a support issue or to invite you to take part in a survey. This processing is necessary to serve our legitimate interest.

Children. This Site is not directed toward children nor does mau5trap knowingly collect information from children without parental consent except where in compliance with applicable laws. If, following a notification by a parent or guardian or upon discovery, a child under sixteen has been improperly registered, we will delete the child’s personal information from our records.

HOW WE MAY SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION 

mau5trap uses a variety of third-party vendors to carry out services like websites management and hosting, online Product purchases and shipping, credit card processing and email communications.

We only share your personal data as necessary, such as to complete a transaction or to provide a Product or Service you have requested or authorized and only with vendors or agents working on our behalf for the purposes described in this

Policy. It is our legitimate interest to share information with these parties for these purposes. For questions about third- party vendors, please send an email to privacy@mau5trap.com.

When legally required, strictly necessary for the performance of the services or to protect our rights, or the rights of our affiliates or users, we disclose your personal information to law enforcement authorities, investigative organizations, our affiliates or in legal proceedings.

We may share your personal information in the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets. Of course, we shall notify you via email and/or a prominent notice on our website and inform you of your rights.

We share data in aggregate form and/or in a form which does not enable the recipient of such data to identify you, with third parties, for example, for industry analysis.

Please note, our Site includes links to products or applications of third parties whose privacy practices may differ from mau5trap. If you provide personal data to any of those third parties or their products, your data is governed by their privacy statements, and we encourage you to read these privacy statements carefully.

International Transfers. Our sharing your personal data in accordance with this Policy may involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Where necessary, we will transfer your personal information in compliance with applicable data protection laws and will implement suitable safeguards to ensure that your personal information is adequately secured by any third party that will access your information (for instance, by using the Standard Contractual Clauses as approved by the European Commission).

If you have questions or wish to obtain more information about the international transfer of your personal information or the implemented safeguards, please send us an email to privacy@mau5trap.com.

DATA SECURITY AND STORAGE 

We may use your personal information for our legitimate interests. For example, we rely on our legitimate interest to analyze and improve our mau5trap Products and Services and the content on our websites, to send you notifications about mau5trap Products and Services or to use your personal information for administrative, fraud detection or legal purposes. Where we process your personal information based on our legitimate interest and no opt-out mechanism is available to you (e.g. in your mau5trap Product settings), you may exercise your right to object by sending an email to privacy@mau5trap.com.

mau5trap is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. However, while we take reasonable precautions to guard the personal information we collect, no security system is impenetrable.

We use a variety of appropriate technical and organizational measures and industry standards to protect your personal information and help prevent information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. For example, we store the personal data you provide on computer systems that have limited access and are in controlled facilities. Additionally, we ensure that our third-party data center vendors provide adequate security measures. Additionally, your data is protected with encryption. Moreover, your password is stored using one-way hash, which means that it cannot be recovered (or disclosed) by anyone, including mau5trap (it can only be reset).

You can only access your mau5trap account information and our service through the use of an individual user login and password. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. Please alert us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. Additionally, always log out and close your browser when you finish your session. Please note, we will never ask you to disclose your password.

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at privacy@mau5trap.com.

Storage. Personal data collected by mau5trap may be stored and processed in your region, in the United States (for instance in our major data centers), or in any other country where mau5trap or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers are located or maintain facilities. mau5trap has put in place adequate mechanisms to protect personal information when it is transferred internationally, for example by using the Standard Contractual Clauses as approved by the European Commission.

mau5trap will retain your personal information for as long as we deem it necessary to enable you to use the website and your mau5trap Product, to provide services to you, to comply with applicable laws (including those regarding document retention), resolve disputes with any parties and otherwise as necessary to allow us to conduct our business. All personal information we retain will be subject to this Policy and our internal retention guidelines. If you have a question about a specific retention period for certain types of personal information we process about you, please send an email to privacy@mau5trap.com.

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES We want you to be in control of how your personal information is used by us. Subject to local law, you can do this in the following ways:

  * you can ask us for a copy of the personal information we hold about you;
  * you can inform us of any changes to your personal information, or if you want us to correct any of the personal information we hold about you;
  * in certain situations, you can ask us to erase, block or restrict the personal information we hold about you, or object to particular ways in which we are using your personal information; and
  * in certain situations, you can also ask us to send the personal information you have given us to a third party.

Where we are using your personal information on the basis of your consent, you are entitled to withdraw that consent at any time. Moreover, where we process your personal information based on legitimate interest or the public interest, you have the right to object at any time to that use of your personal information.

We rely on you to ensure that your personal information is complete, accurate and current. Please inform us promptly of any changes to, or inaccuracies of, your personal information by contacting privacy@mau5trap.com.

We will respond to your request as soon as possible but certainly within 30 days. For more information about how you can control the collection and use of additional usage data and your communication, marketing and advertising preferences, please continue reading below.

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concern you may have about our use of your personal information. If, however, you believe that we have not been able to assist with your complaint or concern, you may have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority in your country (if one exists in your country) or supervisory authority.

mau5trap Account. If you wish to access, edit or remove profile information, change your password, close your account or request deletion of your personal data, you can do it by logging in to your mau5trap account or mau5trap app or sending an email to privacy@mau5trap.com. If you cannot access certain personal information collected by mau5trap via the mau5trap account, you can always contact us by sending an email to privacy@mau5trap.com. We will respond to any request to access or delete your personal data as soon as possible but certainly within 30 days.

Your Communication, Marketing and Advertising Preferences. You can opt out of receiving direct marketing communications from mau5trap by following the instructions included in every email sent to you via the “Unsubscribe” tab. You can also opt out of email subscriptions by updating your Profile and Contact Options in your mau5trap account. We respect your choice, and we will stop sending you promotional emails once you unsubscribe or change your communication settings.

Please note, regardless of your communication settings, we will continue to communicate with you regarding changes to terms and conditions, policy updates, routine customer service messages such as information about current or past purchase, delivery of products, service interruptions, or data breaches.

You can adjust the amount of interest based advertising you may receive by changing your cookie settings, and/or opting out of certain advertising networks. If you have opted out of receiving emails from us, we will not use your email for interest- based advertising activities. For more information about our use of interest-based advertising, please visit our Cookies and Tracking Technologies section.

Your California Privacy Rights. California residents may opt out of having their personally identifiable information shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes by contacting us as described in the “Contact” section. Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a user communicates. There is no industry standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. mau5trap currently does not take action in response to these signals.

How to Control Identifier Settings. You can control how these identifiers are used, including the ability to reset them, through your device settings. Below you can learn about how to control cookie settings on popular web browsers:

  * Apple iOS
  * Android

mau5trap may work with third-party advertisers that use cookies and similar technologies to provide more relevant advertising about mau5trap Products and Services on our websites and across the internet. To provide this ‘interest-based advertising’, the parties combine non-personal data about your online activities acquired over time, which help cater advertising that we deliver to you. Examples of this may include a mau5trap advertisement on a Facebook page, or a Google-owned page such as a search results page or YouTube, or on a site within Google’s advertising network. We do not share your personal information as part of this process. Where necessary we obtain your consent to this process. At all times, you can opt out of these personalized ads from third-party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI websites and DAA websites. Opting out may make the ads you see across the internet less relevant to you.

If you have opted out of receiving communications from us, we will not use your email for interest-based advertising. If you have any questions about the use of your personal information, please send an email to privacy@mau5trap.com.

mau5trap may modify or update this Policy when necessary to reflect customer feedback and changes in our mau5trap Products and Service. Please review it regularly. When we update this Policy, we will revise the ‘Last Update’ date at the top of the Policy. If there are material changes to the Policy or in how mau5trap uses your personal data, we will notify you either by posting a notice of such changes before they take effect or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to regularly review this Policy to learn more how mau5trap is using and protecting your information.

COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES 

We use cookies and similar technologies like pixels, tags, web beacons, and other identifiers to help us personalize our websites for you, remember your preferences, understand how users are using our websites or app, and help customize our marketing offerings.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. This helps us to provide you with a smooth browsing experience and allows us to improve our Site and provide you with tailored content and advertising.

Most web browsers allow you to control cookies through their settings preferences. However, if you limit the ability of websites to set cookies, you may impact your overall user experience. Some browsers offer a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signal whereby you may indicate your preference regarding tracking and cross-site tracking. Although we do not currently employ technology that recognizes DNT signals, we will only process your personal data in accordance with this Policy. For more information on managing cookies, please go to www.allaboutcookies.org, or visit www.youronlinechoices.eu which has further information about behavioural advertising and online privacy. Pixels

Type of Cookie Purpose of Cookie Strictly Necessary These cookies are essential in order to enable you to browse our Site and use its features. The information collected by these cookies relate to the operation of our Site, for example website scripting language and security tokens to maintain secure areas of our Site, including shopping baskets.

Type of Cookie Purpose of Cookie Performance / Analytics These cookies collect anonymous information about how you use our Site, like most visited pages, whether you receive any error messages, and how you arrived at our Site. Information collected by these cookies is used for optimization and never identifies you. These cookies are sometimes placed by third-party providers of web traffic analysis services, such as Google Analytics.

Functional These cookies remember choices you make, for example the country you visit our Site from and your language to improve your experience of our Site. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and cannot be used to track your browsing activity on other websites. Targeting or Advertising These cookies collect information about your browsing habits and inferred interests in order to make advertising more relevant to you. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert, as well as to measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. These cookies are usually placed by third-party advertising networks. They remember the other websites that you visit and this information is shared with third-party organisations, for example advertisers. Social Media These cookies allow you to share what you’ve been doing on our Site with social media organisations such as Facebook and Twitter. These cookies are not within our control. Please refer to the privacy policies of these organisations for how their cookies work.

Please note that third parties may use cookies over which we have no control.

We may use cookies:

  * to collect anonymized data on users behaviour on the site. We may also capture what site a user has come from and what site they go to and also some demographic data (e.g. the user’s location) and we may use that data to analyse user behavior across multiple sites;
  * to categorize pools of users (on an anonymised basis) based on demographic and/or behavioural data and use this to target our advertising.

Web Beacons. We, or our third-party partners, may employ a software technology called web beacons (also known as web bugs, clear gifs or pixels) which helps us understand what content is effective, for example by counting the number of users who have visited these pages, and to understand usage patterns. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to let us know when content is viewed. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded on web pages, ads, and e-mail. We, or our third-party partners, may tie the information gathered by web beacons to the other information we collect about you.

In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies as described above, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative, Digital Advertising Alliance, or European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.

USERS OF SITES IN THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA 

This section of this Policy applies only if you use the Site from a country that is a Member State of the European Economic Area, and supplements the information in this Policy.

Legal Basis for Data Processing. We process personal data for the purposes set out in this Policy, as described above. Our legal basis to process personal data includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of the contract between you and us (for example, to provide you with the services you request and to identify and authenticate you so you may use the Site); necessary to comply with legal requirements (for example, to comply with applicable accounting rules and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement); necessary for our legitimate interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you and to improve the Site); and based on consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our products and services and provide you with marketing information), which may subsequently be withdrawn at any time (by using preference settings in emails or on our Sites, using this form, or emailing us as set out in the Contact section) without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

We may use automated decision-making technologies, including profiling, to support our data processing activities. Our automated decision-making capabilities include logic that attempts to identify artists, music, communications, products, or offers that we believe may interest you. By using this logic, it helps us personalize your interactions with mau5trap and mau5trap artists. For you, this means that you may see online advertisements, direct marketing communications (if you have subscribed), or other advertising or marketing messages or special offers based on your activity on our Sites or interactions with mau5trap or our third-party partners.

In some instances, you may be required to provide us with personal data for processing as described above, in order for us to be able to provide you to use all the features of the Site.
